Eun-Kyo Jeong Product Designer

"She's open to discussions and very approachable, hence an awesome communicator making work easier." - Peer Review 2018

I am a designer with 6 years and 2 months of experience which have shaped up my technical skills for a top-notch design. From launching an app in my recent job, I have learned that 'Perfection comes from the details.'

eunkyojeongdesign@gmail.com +82-10-2007-7774

WORK EXPERIENCE

Daum Webtoon Company Product Designer

Daum Webtoon("Web" and "Cartoon" combined), which has 1M daily users, is the world's first vertical web-comics service from Kakao corp., one of the major IT companies in Korea.

- Major contribution as one of 3 key product designers in launching redesigned iOS, Android apps. (featured 3 times on iOS App Store / ranked 3rd on the comics chart on Google Play Store)
- Coordinated design process from ideating, wireframing, and prototyping, with internal UX team, and created pixel-perfect mocks for the development team through all web & app platforms.
- Conducted user research sessions with marketing team and benchmarked product features and designs, and presented new ideas for internal stakeholder buy-in.

SEP 2016 - APR 2019 (2Y 6M), KOREA

Hanssem UI/UX Designer

No.1 furniture company in Korea.

- Designed and launched a new integrated platform combining portal and commerce, collaborating with PM and development team.
- Conducted benchmarking on Delivery and 3D Modeler service, and defined the flow and main features of the services with UX designers.

JAN - AUG 2016 (8M), KOREA

OFFIN UI/UX Designer / Co-founder

- Launched a fashion O2O app connecting offline stores and customers online, working closely with engineers.
- Presented the app at Korea's biggest startup and technology conference, and was featured as top 20 promising startups in 2014 by Digital Inside Media.

APR - OCT 2014 (8M), KOREA

Soram Hospital Freelance UI/UX Designer

Redesigned, and launched a user-friendly website for Soram hospital which led to a 10 times increase in hotline calls made on a daily basis.

SEP - DEC 2015 (4M), KOREA

LG Electronics UX Design Intern

- Researched and proposed new lifestyle concepts of Seamless Screen UX, and designed interaction models for the future generation.
- \bullet Generated Persona and Scenario regarding IoT, and created prototypes with the mockups.

JUN - SEP 2013 (3M), KOREA

Gabia UI/UX Design Intern

No.1 Internet business solution company in Korea.

- Redesigned Gabia website to maximize its usability, and presented it to internal stakeholders.
- Presented 2015 Internet Trend Report at an executive meeting and proposed future vision.

JUL - AUG 2015 (2M), KOREA

Danawa Web Designer

One of the biggest price comparison websites in Korea

Designed commerce events and published HTML/CSS.

MAR - NOV 2011 (9M), KOREA

Hmart Head Office Design Intern

Designed on/offline advertisement that entailed photographing & printing tasks.

DEC 2011 - OCT 2012(10M), U.S.A

EDUCATION

Hong-ik University

B.F.A. Visual Communication Design

- Scholarship Recipient (3yrs)
- Best presentation in Service Design 2013 (1/20+ teams)

MAR 2008 - AUG 2014 SEOUL, KOREA

Kipfa UX Design School

Studied UX methodology then applied them in practical service.

MAY - JUN 2014 5 WEEKS (200 HRS), KOREA

SKILLS

Design

Visual Design Interation Design Mobile Design Motion Graphics Branding & Identity Illutration

UX Methods

Storyboarding
Journey Mapping
Persona & Scenario
Low to High Fidelity Design
Wireframing & Prototyping
Usability Testing

Tools

Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, InDesign, XD, Sketch, InVision, Craft Flinto, Principle, Figma Framer.js, HTML/CSS